0. Group member
ShanLuo, MingCao
1. Introduce System Functionality
The final functionality we achieved for our system is far more complicated and interesting than we planned at the beginning. Overall, the system allows you to input  a name of location or a pair of coordinates, and it will give back a map that contains the markers showing  the nearest areas to that location as well as the basic information about these areas. And when clicking on the marker, the name of the location will be shown. There are about 2.2 million U.S. area informations stored in this system which is a challenging number even for some basic microsoft office programs.
2. How to setup the system
The setup is easy. You only need to follow the instructions below and it will run without error.
I. First thing first, you should install javafx on your eclipse. You can follow the following steps to install it:
a. Open eclipse.
b. Click help.
c. Choose Eclipse Marketplace...
d.In the search bar, input javafx and press return.
e. The first result "e(fx)clipse 2.4.0" is what you need to install. Click on install and follow its instruction to finish the installation. That's it!
II. After you download the archived file, extract it first. You will see a "Final Project" folder. Open it and you will see a "FinalProject" folder, two files, usmap.gif and googlemap.html and two png files containing UML diagarams . Create a new project in eclipse, then import the "FinalProject" folder into the project. 
III. After you import the folder, there will be a bin folder under your eclipse new project folder. You need to move the usmap.gif and googlemap.html file into the bin folder.
3.  How to run the system and what the system can achieve
Run under the main.java. It needs several seconds to initialize the program before open a log in window. Type "user" in the username textfield, "123"for the password textfield, and then press login. It would take several seconds to construct dataset.
It would then show a new window. On the left side is a map and a textarea which would show information of areas under that map. On the right side, you can first choose how you want to search for an area. You can either choose inputting a location name or a pair of coordinates. The system only includes U.S geological data, so if you want to try a location outside a America, it wouldn't give back a right return. Otherwise, it would be fine.
There are also a field that you should type in how many nearest areas you want it gives back. Beccause the limitation of google map, it cannot mark a lot of locations on a same map. But if you just try a number around 10, it should be fine.
Last but not the least, there is a combo box where you can choose state to limit the area you search for. If you don't know which state you want to search for, you can choose "ALL STATES" option. But keep in mind that, choosing a state could increase the accuracy of the results.
After input everything, just click the search button. You will have your results showing on both map and info section. Remember, you can always adjust the map however you like because it's a full-function google map!
4.  Others need to be noticed
If you choose the coordinate model and type in character in the coordinate fields, it will show "Invalid input".
If you don't type in a integer into the choosing-number-field, it will show "Invalid input".
You can search again after each search! No worry.
The url of our repo on github is https://github.com/mingcaocao/GIS.